mysilpada.com 2016-04-29

# Silpada | Privacy Policy

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY PRIOR TO USING THIS SITE. BY USING THE SITE, YOU INDICATE YOUR AGREEMENT WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE PRIVACY POLICY, DO NOT USE THIS SITE.

Thank you for visiting our website. Silpada Designs respects the privacy of every individual who visits our websites and online areas. We are committed to protecting the privacy of the visitors to our websites and our independent Representatives. This Policy outlines the information Silpada Designs will collect, and how we will use that information. It applies to your use of silpada.com and any other website owned or operated by Silpada Designs.

### Collection of Information

We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when provided by our visitors. (You are free to browse our Sites without submitting personal information.) The information you provide is only used to fulfill a specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner (for example, to add you to one of our mailing lists). We may retain and use your personal information for several purposes. For instance, we may store and process your information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services. We may also use your email address to send you updates about new products or follow up with you if you have attempted to complete an Application to become a Silpada Designs Representative but did not complete the process. Silpada Designs does not intend to collect any personal information (such as name, address, telephone number, age or email address) from persons under the age of 18.

### Cookies and Tracking Technology

When you view one of our websites, we may store some information in the form of a "cookie " or similar file that is automatically downloaded to your computer. Cookies are small files that enable us to better customize your online experience with us. For instance, cookies may assist us in tailoring a web page or advertisement to better match your interests and preferences. Information gathered through cookies may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, the time spent at our website, and websites visited just before and just after visiting our websites. Please be assured that cookies are safe. They are not programs that can be used to damage files and your personal information cannot be gathered from them. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although, in that case, you may not be able to use certain features on our Site. In addition, Silpada Designs may log the Internet Protocol ("IP") address of the location from where you are visiting our websites. This is a security measure to protect our company information and detect fraud.

### Our Use of Your Information

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our independent Representatives and online visitors. We may also use your personal information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, inform you of services or products, customize your experience, or to detect and protect us against error, fraud or other criminal activity. We may share your personal information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: 1) permitted or required by law; 2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized activity; or, 3) investigating fraud that has already taken place. The information provided to these entities is not for marketing purposes. As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. The personal information we gather about you is generally considered one of the transferable business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers or any dissolution.

### Links to Other Sites

Silpada Designs cannot ensure the protection of any personal information you provide to a third-party website that links to or from any of our websites, since these third-party sites are owned and operated independently. These third-party sites may have their own separate privacy policies beyond our control. As such, we cannot assume responsibility or liability whatsoever for practices, actions or policies of these third-party sites.

### Security

We understand that you may be concerned about the privacy and confidentiality of your personal information. Rest assured we have taken precautions to ensure that this information is safe and secure. Only authorized employees, agents or contractors (who have agreed to keep your information secure and confidential) have access to this information. That being said, please be aware that no data transmission over the Internet will be 100 percent secure. While we take steps to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

### Revisions to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change or revise this Policy at any time. You should periodically visit this page to determine the current Privacy Policy. Your continued use of our websites, following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy, will signify your acceptance of those changes.

### Designated Agent Contact Information

If you have any questions, concerns or comments about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us using one of the methods below:  
By email: [compliance@silpada.com](mailto:compliance@silpada.com)  
By phone: 1.913.851.7757
